Guide to the School of Management, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Management, Yale University, records
1964-2014
RU 486
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
36.75
(61 boxes)
The records consist of administrative files, grade reports, admission files, a survey, registrar notebooks, financial aid records, and committee files documenting the establishment of and search for a dean of the Yale School of Organization and Management (known as the School of Management after 1995).
Yale University. School of Management
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 30-A (YRG 30-A), Central records and records of the dean of the Yale School of Management.
Conditions Governing Access
While this collection as a whole is available for research, parts of it may be restricted due to law, university policy or fragility. Any restricted material will be noted as such.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of administrative files, grade reports, admission files, a survey, registrar notebooks, financial aid records, and committee files documenting the establishment of and search for a dean of the Yale School of Organization and Management (known as the School of Management after 1995) as well as the records of Professor Clayton P. Alderfer, former Director of Professional Studies.
Business schools; Management -- Study and teaching; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. School of Management; Yale University. School of Organization and Management
- Records, 1964-1986; Accession 1994-A-029
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2021
  - Documents Regarding the Establishment of SOM, 1964-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Management Education at Yale By John Perry Miller, 1986 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - SOM Miscellaneous, 1974-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Professional Masters Program, Establishment of at SOM, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - SOM Conference (Search Committee), 1974 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Search Committee for the Dean of SOM
    - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - MeetincpNotices and Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Nominations, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10 - 12)
- Grade reports, 1976-1997; Accession 2002-A-120
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1976 Fall Term (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1977 Spring Term (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1977 Fall Term (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1978 Spring Term (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1978 Fall Term (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1979 Spring Term (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1979 Fall Term (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1980 Spring Term (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1980 Fall Term (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1981 Spring Term (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1981 Fall Term (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1982 Spring Term (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1982 Fall Term (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1983 Spring Term (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1983 Fall Term (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1984 Spring Term (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1984 Fall Term (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1985 Spring Term (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1985 Fall Term (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1986 Spring Term (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1986 Fall Term (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1987 Spring Term (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1987 Fall Term (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1988 Spring Term (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1988 Fall Term (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1989 Spring Term (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 1989 Fall Term (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 1990 Spring Term (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - 1990 Fall Term (PPM Courses) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 1990 Fall Term (Non-PPM Courses) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 1991 Spring Term (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 1991 Fall Term (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 1992 Spring Term (PPM Courses) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 1992 Spring Term (Non-PPM Courses) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 1992 Fall Term (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 1993 Spring Term (PPM Courses) (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - 1993 Spring Term (Non-PPM Courses) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 1993 Fall Term (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - 1994 Spring Term (PPM Courses) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 1994 Spring Term (Non-PPM Courses) (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - 1994 Fall Term (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 1995 Spring Term (PPM Courses) (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 1995 Spring Term (Non-PPM Courses) (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - 1995 Fall Term (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - 1996 Spring Term (PPM Courses) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - 1996 Spring Term (Non-PPM Courses) (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - 1996 Fall Term (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - 1997 Spring Term (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Profiles and statistics concerning student admissions, 1978-2000; Accession 2004-A-079
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2035
  - Class of 1978-Profiles and Statistics (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1979-Profiles and Statistics (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report - Class of 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1980-Profiles and Statistics (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ADMISSIONS FINAL REPORTS - Class 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1981-Profiles and Statistics (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report - Class of 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report - Class of 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report - Class of '83/Statistics - '83, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Class of '84 Statistics, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ADMISSIONS REPORT 1981-82 Class of 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Statistics, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Statistics, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - STATISTICS, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - More '86 STATISTICS., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - GMAT & GRE SCORES, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - STATISTICS - APPLICANTS/Enrolled & not enrolled, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - MISC. STATISTICS, LISTS, ETC. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - STATISTICS, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Statistics Profiles, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Statistics Misc./GMAT, GRE, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Statistics Misc., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1988 PROFILES (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Misc. Statistics, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Misc. Reports, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Statistics GMAT-GRE, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Misc. Statistics/ Statistics GMAT-GRE, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Staff Evaluations (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Misc. Statistics, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Statistics GMAT-GRE/Inquiries & App. Flow/A.R.R., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Profiles, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 31 - 32)
  - MISC. STATISTICS, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - SCORES, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - PROFILES, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - "SO-FAR", 1992 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - PROFILES II, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - "SO-FAR", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - PROFILES, CLASS OF 1993 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - SUB-POPULATION PROFILES, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - PROFILES '93, VOL. 2, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - STATISTICS '93/UPDATE REPORTS, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - PROFILES VOL., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 43 - 44)
  - "SO-FAR", 1994 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - GENERAL STATISTICS, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - PROFILES, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 47 - 48)
  - "SO-FAR", 1995 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - MISC. STATISTICS, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - PROFILES II, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - GENERAL STATISTICS, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - MISC. SUMMARY STATISTICS/ VARIOUS YEARS - ONGOING (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - "SO-FAR", 1996 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - PROFILES, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 55 - 56)
  - "INQUIRY", 1996 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - "SO-FAR", 1997 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - PROFILE, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - PROFILES, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 60 - 61)
  - MISC. STATISTICS, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - STATISTICS, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - MCRPTG/ADMRPTG - ALTERNATE PROFILE VERSIONS (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - "SO-FAR", 1998 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - SO-FAR, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - STATISTICS, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - "WE" STUDY (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - INQUIRY STATISTICS, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - CLASS OF 1999 PROFILES (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - PROFILES, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - MISC., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Publications DATA, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - CLASS OF '96 ENTRANCE SURVEY, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - CLASS OF '96 S.O.M. SURVEY, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- "What's on Your Mind? State-of-the-School Questionnaire" student survey results, 2000; Accession 2006-A-191
  - Student survey results, 2000 (Box 1)
- Administrative records and video recordings of the Office of Communications, 1998-2003; Accession 2007-A-164
  The materials are open for research with the exception of material in box 1, folder 2, which is restricted until January 1, 2038 due to University policy.
  - Administrative records
    - Publications Guide, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Yale School of Management Investment Prospectus (Draft), 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      The materials in this folder is restricted until January 1, 2038 due to University policy.
    - SOM Coat of Arms and Logotype, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Videorecordings
    - "Yale MBA" Japanese, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 2)
    - "Yale MBA" Spanish, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 3)
    - "Yale SOM" Chinese, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 4)
    - Yale vs Harvard Debate, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Yale MBA (Third Cut), 2000 July 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 6)
    - Yale MBA, 2000 July 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Yale MBA, 2000 August 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Yale MBA, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Student Interviews (last day of taping), 2000; videotape (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Yale SOM Faculty Interviews, 2001; videotape (VHS) (Box 11)
    - Yale Approval Copy, 2000 August 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 12)
    - Yale School of Management Interviews, 2001 December 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 13)
    - A Meeting of Minds: Techniques for Interviewing SOM Candidates, 1996 October 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 14)
    - Yale University: Raw Footage, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 15)
    - Yale MBA, undated; videotape (Betacam-SP) (Box 16)
    - Yale Review, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 17)
    - Dean Garten's Speech, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - Yale SOM Commencement, 2001; videotape (VHS) (Box 21)
    - Yale SOM Graduation, 2000; videotape (VHS) (Box 22)
- Records, 1976-1997; Accession 2007-A-233
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2033
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Courses, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Courses, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Internships, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Newsleter, 1978, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, 1980s-1990s (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Syllabi, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Records, 1997-2000; Accession 2013-A-074
  Restricted until January 1, 2075
  - Grade reports
    - Grade Reports: Miscellaneous Course Check List, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Perspectives on Management, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 505 Tax Planning for Individuals, Small …, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 510 Data Analysis and Statistics, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 520 Economic Analysis, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 521 Macroeconomic Analysis, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 523 Managerial Negotiation, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 525 Competitive and Cooperative Strategies, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 527 Strategic Management of Nonprofit Organizations, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 528 The Environment: Public and Private Management, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 529 Practice and Management of Creativity and Innovation, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 538 Managing Strategic Change, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 541 Corporate Finance, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 543 Financial Instruments and Contracts, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 549 Derivatives and Financial Engineering, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 552 Marketing Research, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 558 Consumer Behavior, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 559 Marketing Strategy, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 572 Operations Management II, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 577 Russia's Emerging Capitalism and Market, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 578 China as an Emerging Market, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 579 The International Firm and the Nation State, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 580 Business, Government and the International Economy, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 582 East Asia in the World Economy, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 589 Information Technology for Management, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 611 Policy Modeling, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 615 Active Investing: Theory, Practice, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 621 Theory and History of Money and Financial Institutions, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 625 Corporate Strategies: Case Study Approach, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 635 Venture Capital and Private Equity Investments, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 643 Investment Banking, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 660 Healthcare Delivery System Policy, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 690 and 691 Independent Reading and Research, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 694 Housing and Community Development, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 812 Financial Statement Analysis, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 814 Understanding and Evaluating the Financial Statements of Not-for-Profit Organizations, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 815 Managerial Accounting, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 816 Advanced Managerial Accounting, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 818 Advanced Financial Reporting, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 820 Foreign Exchange and Related Derivative Instruments, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 822 How to Start a High Tech Company, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 832 The Strategic Manager, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 870 Fundamentals of Accounting, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 871 Financial Reporting, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 880 Strategic Environment of Management, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 881 The Politics of Strategic Management, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 890 and 891 Corporate Finance and Options, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 993 National Innovation Systems; Non-SOM Courses, 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Grade Reports: Miscellaneous, Course Checklist, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 17a)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 501 Taxes and Business Planning, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 515 Decision Analysis and Game Theory, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 546 Macroeconomic Analysis, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 522 Economic Analysis of the Public Sector, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 523 Managerial Negotiations, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 525 Competitive Strategies, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 526 Regulation Strategy Telecommunications, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 542 International Finance, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 543 Financial Instruments and Contracts, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 544 Investment Management, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 545 Financial Engineering, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 547 Fixed Income Security Analysis, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 550 Marketing Management, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 556 International Marketing, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 557 Product Planning and Development, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 571 Operations Management I, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 574 Management of Quality, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 586 Strategy, Technology and War, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 588 Building Competitve Advantage through Information Technology, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 590 Aspects of Investing in Emerging Markets, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 594 Emerging Markets of Latin America, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 618 Entrepreneurship, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 626 New Haven and Problems of Urban Change, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 633 Strategic Human Resource Management, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 635 Venture Capital and Private Equity Investments, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 642 Corporate Finance and Capital Markets, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 658 Cost Effectiveness Analysis and Decision…, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 673 International Strategy and Competition, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 675 TV, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 690 and 691 Independent Reading and Research, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 694 Housing and Community Development, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 696 Introduction to Planning and Development, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 751 Seminar in Marketing II, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 811 Emerging Markets Finance, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 812 Financial Statement Analysis, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 813 Advanced Financial Statement Analysis, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 815 Managerial Accounting, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 817 Individual Tax Planning, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 818 Advanced Financial Reporting, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 819 The Practice of Real Estate I, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 827 Institutional Funds Management, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 828 International Mergers, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 829 The Practice of Real Estate II, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 833 Organizational Communication and Influence, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 843 Strategic Communication and Business Management, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 836 Program Evaluation, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 871 Financial Reporting, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 883 Organizational Communication and Influence, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 885 Foundation of Leaderships and Teams, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 886 Designing and Managing Organizations, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 891 Corporate Finance and Options, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 992 Strategy and Policy in New Health Care…, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Grade Reports: PPM 995 Corporate Governance and the Role of Management, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Grade Reports: Non-SOM courses, 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Grade Reports: Miscellaneous, Course Checklist, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 510 Data Analysis and Statistics, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 520 Economic Analysis, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 521 Macroeconomic Analysis, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 525 Competitive and Cooperative Strategies, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 528 The Environment: Public and Private Management, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 541 Corporate Finance, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 543 Financial Instruments and Contracts, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 544 Investment Management, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 546 International Financial Markets, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 550 Marketing Management, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 555 Pricing Strategy, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 558 Consumer Behavior, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 559 Marketing Strategy, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 572 Operations Management II, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 578 China as an Emerging Market, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 579 Managing Risks, Oppportunities and Challenges in Foreign Markets, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 589 Information Technology for Management, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 596 Post-Communist Transition in Eastern Europe and the Former Soviet Union: Challenges for Business Strategies, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 611 Policy Modeling, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 618 Entrepreneurship, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 621 Theory and History of Money and Financial Institutions, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 635 VC, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 644 Structured Finance, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 690 and MGT 691 (all sections) Independent Study Research, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 694 Housing and Community Development, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 695 Nonprofit Organizations Clinic, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 679 Intermediate Planning and Development, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 808 Introduction to Operations Research, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 809 Managing the Unmanageable, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 810 Global Business Environment, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 812 Financial Statement Analysis, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 813 Advanced Financial Statement Analysis, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 814 Financial Statements for Not-for-Profits, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 815 Managerial Accounting, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 818 Advanced Financial Reporting, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 822 How to Start a High-Tech Company, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 826 Financial Engineering, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 830 Numerical Methods in Options Pricing, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 831 Valuation of Technology, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 835 Transportation Strategy and Management, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 837 Multivariate Methods for Management Consultants, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 838 Listening to the Customer, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 51)